{
  "pyramidMoney": [
    { "id": 1, "amount": "500$" },
    { "id": 2, "amount": "1000$" },
    { "id": 3, "amount": "2000$" },
    { "id": 4, "amount": "4000$" },
    { "id": 5, "amount": "8000$" },
    { "id": 6, "amount": "16000$" },
    { "id": 7, "amount": "32000$" },
    { "id": 8, "amount": "64000$" },
    { "id": 9, "amount": "125000$" },
    { "id": 10, "amount": "250000$" },
    { "id": 11, "amount": "500000$" },
    { "id": 12, "amount": "1000000$" }
  ],

  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "questionText": "What is the capital city of Ukraine?",
      "answers": [" Kyiv", "Kharkiv", "Lviv", "Odessa"],
      "correctAnswer": " Kyiv"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "questionText": "Which river flows through Kyiv?",
      "answers": ["Dnipro", "Danube", "Volga", "Don"],
      "correctAnswer": "Dnipro"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "questionText": "What is the official language of Ukraine?",
      "answers": ["Ukrainian", "Russian", "Polish", "English"],
      "correctAnswer": "Ukrainian"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "questionText": "Which historical site is located in Kyiv?",
      "answers": ["Saint Sophia Cathedral", "Eiffel Tower", "Great Wall of China", "Taj Mahal"],
      "correctAnswer": "Saint Sophia Cathedral"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "questionText": "What is the traditional Ukrainian folk instrument?",
      "answers": ["Bandura", "Accordion", "Guitar", "Violin"],
      "correctAnswer": "Bandura"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "questionText": "Which Ukrainian city is known for its annual Lviv Coffee Festival?",
      "answers": ["Lviv", "Kharkiv", "Kyiv", "Odessa"],
      "correctAnswer": "Lviv"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "questionText": "What is the highest mountain in Ukraine?",
      "answers": ["Hoverla", "Carpathians", "Himalayas", "Mont Blanc"],
      "correctAnswer": "Hoverla"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "questionText": "Which Ukrainian writer was awarded the Nobel Prize in Literature?",
      "answers": ["Taras Shevchenko", "Ivan Franko", "Lesya Ukrainka", "Svitlana Alexievich"],
      "correctAnswer": "Svitlana Alexievich"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "questionText": "What is the traditional Ukrainian dance?",
      "answers": ["Hopak", "Waltz", "Salsa", "Breakdance"],
      "correctAnswer": "Hopak"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "questionText": "Which Ukrainian dish is made from grated potatoes?",
      "answers": ["Deruny", "Borscht", "Varenyky", "Holubtsi"],
      "correctAnswer": "Deruny"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "questionText": "Which Ukrainian city is famous for its annual Odesa International Film Festival?",
      "answers": ["Odessa", "Kyiv", "Lviv", "Kharkiv"],
      "correctAnswer": "Odessa"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "questionText": "Who is the national poet of Ukraine?",
      "answers": ["Taras Shevchenko", "Ivan Franko", "Lesya Ukrainka", "Olena Teliha"],
      "correctAnswer": "Taras Shevchenko"
    }
  ]
}
